alert("Hello");
// Creating an array and passing the number, questions, options and answers

let questions = [
   {
     numb: 1,
     question: "Batman is also known as?",
     answer: "Bruce Wayne",
     options: [
         "Bruce Lee",
         "Bruce Banner",
         "Bruce Wayne",
         "Bruce John"
     ]

   },
   {
     numb: 2,
     question: "Flash is also known as?",
     answer: "Barry Allen",
     options: [
         "Barry Allen",
         "Allen Barry",
         "Allen Barri",
         "Barri Allen"
     ]

   },
   {
     numb: 3,
     question: "What is aquaman's weapon called as?",
     answer: "Trident of Neptune",
     options: [
         "Trident of Amphitrite",
         "Trident of Daxam",
         "Trident of Neptune",
         "Trident of Triton"
     ]

   },
   {
     numb: 4,
     question: "Where did Wonder Woman come from?",
     answer: "Themyscira",
     options: [
         "Themiscira",
         "Myst world",
         "Chomyst",
         "Jemychiara"
     ]

   },
   {
     numb: 5,
     question: "Which planet does Superman come from?",
     answer: "Krypton",
     options: [
         "Daxam",
         "Earth",
         "Neptune",
         "Krypton"
     ]

   },
   {
     numb: 6,
     question: "Batman protects which city?",
     answer: "Gotham City",
     options: [
         "Star City",
         "Central City",
         "Gotham City",
         "Opal City"
     ]

   },
   {
     numb: 7,
     question: "How did Spiderman get his powers?",
     answer: "He was bitten by a spider",
     options: [
         "He was blinded with radioactive components",
         "He was born with powers",
         "He was affected by a chemical explosion",
         "He was bitten by a spider"
     ]

   },
   {
     numb: 8,
     question: "The 'Scarlett Speedster' is the name of which Superhero?",
     answer: "The Flash",
     options: [
         "Speed Ball",
         "The Flash",
         "Star Dust",
         "Hulk"
     ]

   },
   {
     numb: 9,
     question: "Who was the first female superhero of the justice society of America?",
     answer: "Wonder Woman",
     options: [
         "Elektra",
         "Storm",
         "Wonder Woman",
         "Hawkgirl"
     ]

   },
   {
     numb: 10,
     question: "What is Superman's real name in Krypto Planet series?",
     answer: "Kal-el",
     options: [
         "Kal-el",
         "Clark Kent",
         "Jar-el",
         "Herry Kent"
     ]

   }



];
